paycheckcity.com 2015-06-22

# PayCheckCity Privacy Policy

PayCheckCity® believes that privacy is important to the success and use of the Internet. This statement sets forth PAYCHECKCITY®'s Privacy Policy for this website and describes the practices that PAYCHECKCITY® will follow with respect to the privacy of users of this site. Symmetry reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy any time by reasonable notice, including without limitation by posting revised terms on the Site (which shall constitute reasonable notice), and such amended terms will go into effect and shall be binding upon you as soon as they are posted to the Site; thus, you should consult the most recent version of the Privacy Policy each time that you view the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your consent to this Privacy Policy.

This Site is not intended for children, so any persons under the age of 18 should not use this Site. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from our Site about children under the age 13.

_What personal information do we collect?_

PAYCHECKCITY® collects only personal information about you that you choose to provide to us through the Site, such as:

  * Payroll tax calculators: address

  * Newsletter subscription / Contact Us: name, e-mail address, phone number

PAYCHECKCITY® also collects nonpersonal information that helps us to understand site visitor demographics such as company, size of company, industry, job function, etc. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we routinely review and update the adequacy of our security procedures.

_How is information collected, used, and disclosed?_  
We do not share or sell your personal information to anyone. We do not give your personal information to anyone outside of PAYCHECKCITY® for their promotional or marketing use. We do not collect personal information unless we first ask you for it.  If you register to receive newsletters, you may also get periodic emails from PAYCHECKCITY® or our trusted partners. These emails will contain information from companies that offer legitimate products and services typically in the finance, taxation, accounting, or payroll related areas. Again, PAYCHECKCITY® does not share or sell your personally identifiable information to these companies; we directly manage any email campaigns on behalf of these trusted partners. You may always unsubscribe from future newsletters.  Additionally, in some states, in order to provide accurate paycheck calculations we may ask for street addresses.  These are only used to accurately calculate in this locale. We do not store street addresses. Only city and state address information is stored.

Whether you provide any information is entirely up to you. If you have voluntarily provided information, you consent to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy. Also, PAYCHECKCITY® may provide aggregate statistics about visitors to our sites, such as volume, traffic patterns, visitor demographics and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal information. PAYCHECKCITY® may also disclose information in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the Web site Terms and Conditions of Use; or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

Google Analytics is installed as a third party service on PaycheckCity®. Analytics collects demographic and interest data from trusted external sources. Thresholds are applied to prevent anyone viewing a report from inferring the demographics or interests of individual users.

Cookies may be used by third-party advertisers who serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use nonpersonal information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

_What are cookies and how are they used?_  
Some PAYCHECKCITY® sites, like many other commercial web sites, may utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a web site operator determine that a particular user had visited the site previously and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. Cookies are small strings of text that web sites can send to your browser. Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or obtain your e-mail address. If you are simply browsing a PAYCHECKCITY® informational site, a cookie may be used to identify your browser as one that has visited the site before.

We may also make use of memory-based cookies in support of authenticating the user of certain PAYCHECKCITY® web applications. Similarly, we may use cookies so that we can provide information based on preferences you have indicated while using the site. Although you have the ability to modify your browser to either accept all cookies, notify you when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize PAYCHECKCITY® services which require registration if you reject cookies.

_How do we protect your information?_  
We use industry standard techniques, which may include firewalls, encryption, intrusion detection and site monitoring to protect your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via e-mail. We have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our servers. Internally, we will restrict access to your information to employees who need access to the information in order to do their jobs. These employees are limited in number, and are committed to our privacy policies. We will review our security arrangements from time to time as we deem appropriate.

_How can you help protect your information?_  
If you are using a PAYCHECKCITY® web site for which you registered and chose an Access Code, we recommend that you do not divulge your Access Code to anyone. We will never ask you for your Access Code in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Also remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if others have access to your computer.

_Is your information protected when you leave our Site?_

Other PAYCHECKCITY® sites may contain links to other sites, including those of our business partners. While we seek to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites. You should review the privacy policy of any sites that you visit in order to determine what information about you is collected and how that information is used.

Questions?

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please [contact us](http://www.paycheckcity.com/pages/contact-us.php).

Last Updated: March 19, 2015

[Contact PaycheckCity®](http://www.paycheckcity.com/pages/contact-us.php) for more information about our [payroll withholding calculators](http://www.paycheckcity.com/pages/private-label-calculators.php), and other payroll tools including the [Symmetry Tax Engine®](http://www.paycheckcity.com/pages/ste.php) and [private-label paycheck calculators](http://www.paycheckcity.com/pages/private-label-calculators.php).

Last Updated on Thursday, March 19, 2015
